'use strict';

const STORE = [
    {
      question: 'How many finals has Mahendra Singh Dhoni played in the IPL?',
      answers: [
        '5',
        '7',
        '3',
        '6'
        ],
      correctAnswer: '7'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which cricketer has scored the fastest hundred in the IPL?',
      answers: [
        'Virat Kohli',
        'David Warner',
        'Chris Gayle',
        'Yusuf Pathan'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Chris Gayle'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which team has successfully defended its title in the IPL?',
      answers: [
        'Chennai Super Kings',
        'Kolkatta Knight Riders',
        'Deccan Chargers',
        'Mumbai Indians'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Chennai Super Kings'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which cricketer scored four hundreds in the 2016 IPL?',
      answers: [
        'Jacques Kallis',
        'Virat Kohli',
        'Suresh Raina',
        'Brendon Mccullum'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Virat Kohli'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which cricketer hit the winning runs for Rajasthan Royals in the 2008 IPL?',
      answers: [
        'Shane Warne',
        'Graeme Smith',
        'Sohail Tanvir',
        'Yusuf Pathan'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Sohail Tanvir'
    },
    {
      question: 'How many teams has Parthiv Patel represented before IPL 2018?',
      answers: [
        '6',
        '2',
        '4',
        '1'
        ],
      correctAnswer: '6'
    },
    {
      question: 'How many foreign (overseas) captains have won the IPL?',
      answers: [
      '4',
      '3',
      '0',
      '2'
      ],
      correctAnswer: '3'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which cricketer has bowled the most number of dot balls?',
      answers: [
        'Praveen Kumar',
        'Lasith Malinga',
        'Harbhajan Singh',
        'Sunil Narine'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Praveen Kumar'
    },
    {
      question: 'How many number of hat-tricks have taken place in the IPL',
      answers: [
      '10',
      '12',
      '4',
      '17'
      ],
      correctAnswer: '17'
    },
    {
      question: 'How many balls did Yusuf Pathan take to score hundred against MI in IPL 2010?',
      answers: [
        '37',
        '40',
        '34',
        '31'
    ],
    correctAnswer: '37'
    }
];
